[music]
>> Hi guys. Today's beauty maintenance day,
so I can't wait to take you guys along
with me. Another beautiful day in
London. I am on my way to get my hair
blow dried.
>> [music]
[music]
>> I'm loving the blow dry, guys. I feel
like every time I get a blow dry, I feel
like myself again.
But now I am on my way to Asma. She is
the best aesthetician that I always go
to in London. Your girl is due for some
serious touch up. Okay, guys. So, I'm
back at Skin Medical.
She just changed locations, but it's so
stunning here.
Hey guys, so we are cleaning up the area
for injection.
We're getting Anna some more ready. Mhm.
Just on time.
Much needed.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Hey guys. So, since I am flying out to
Mykonos tomorrow, I just wanted to put
you guys on to something, which is the
HolaFly plans eSIM. Honestly, it has
saved my life. This is my travel go-to.
Every single time I'm in a new country,
before I get there, I always make sure I
buy the eSIM because from the moment you
land, you're covered. Like, I don't have
to stress about airport Wi-Fi. I can
literally just book an Uber straight
away. I can navigate around town and not
feeling stressed and just having Google
Maps, it just really helps you. I was so
happy when they reached out to me to
partner up together because I was like,
"I always use you guys." So, this
literally aligns with me perfectly. So,
yeah, I'm just so happy because I'm
like, "Oh my god, like I can finally
share this with you guys."
Hi guys. Today is a very exciting day
because we are going on a trip. We're
going to Mykonos. Yeah. This is my third
time in Mykonos. Last year I went two
times cuz I had so much fun. And most
importantly, it is the start of our Euro
summer. Guys, this trip literally came
out of nowhere. This [\h__\h] happened two
days ago. I was in bed. I was so bored
and I was like, "I don't want to be in
London. Like, it's so hot." So, I called
my girl, "Hey,
let's go. Let's fly." And she was like,
"You know what? I'm down." I just love
friends that are down for spontaneous
trips because we literally look for
hotels, the next day we booked the
flights and the hotel, and now, two days
later, I'm on my way to the airport.
That's how the best trips come about.
Spontaneous, it's last minute. You don't
expect anything. That's why I had to go
get my nails done so quickly and I got
them so basic because I had no time to
even get ready. I've been packing the
whole of yesterday, but I'm so excited
to come back to Mykonos, be under the
sun, tan, enjoy myself, relax with my
girls, and just have a good time.
So, yeah, it is currently 8:00 a.m. and
I'm on my way to the airport. My
flight's at 12:00, so hopefully we have
some time to do some shopping. I really
want to look for a nice pair of
Havaianas. Okay, guys, so I've already
passed security. My airport outfit, I'm
wearing this set from IMGIA, and as you
can see, I'm supporting France, well,
France and England.
So, I got to make it fair, you know?
France on the outside and England is
where my heart's at. So, whoever wins
the World Cup, I'm all for. I managed to
get some bread so I can eat some food on
the plane. I definitely don't like plane
food.
We're in Mykonos!
The sun is out. I feel so good.
Can't wait to get to the hotel. I'm
ready to have the best time of my life.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Okay, guys, made it to the hotel.
Apparently, it's brand new.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Wow, guys, so the hotel's been only open
for 1 week. Look how beautiful [music]
this is.
Wow, it's 6:00 p.m. and it looks like
this. Apparently, the view gets better
even when it gets darker.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Guys, this is the room tour. I literally
booked this so last minute, so
everything was sold out.
She's kind of tiny, but I think she's
cute.
I wish we had like a little balcony and
a pool.
But it's cute. The first thing I like to
do when I get on holiday is to unpack
all of my stuff, so like this I have all
of my stuff laid out and I can just get
ready easier. So, unpack with me. I'm
here for 6 days, 5 nights. Guys, look
how beautiful this dress is.
I can't wait to wear her.
>> [music]
>> I'm so obsessed with these heels. I just
bought them from Jack's News
>> [music]
>> and the yellow peep toe.
She is so stunning. Can't wait to wear
her. My favorite hack is when I travel,
I love to put my sunnies inside the bag,
so it kind of gives it a little cushion
and the bag doesn't get mashed up. Like
I put head scarf, little glasses,
whatever you guys got, just put them
inside the bags.
>> [music]
[music]
>> It's sound right, boy.
>> [music]
[music]
>> So this is the full complete unpacking.
This is where I have all of my sliders,
my heels. These are my daytime clothes,
my bikinis, my cover-ups. So down here I
have all of my hair wands, my jewelry,
my bags. [music]
And then up here we have the hats.
Obviously we've got the dresses hanging.
I just think it looks so pretty. Over
here we have all of the skin care. Then
we've got the makeup. And then the hair
products on this side because, you know,
we've got the plug over here so it's
easy and convenient.
>> Look at the sunset. It's so pretty.
>> I'm with Amy.
>> Hey guys.
>> How are you feeling to be in Greece?
Second year in a row.
Ask me why.
We are walking down this huge ass hill.
We should have worn trainers for sure.
And I'm wearing my Apple outfit because
I wasn't expecting it to be this windy
in Mykonos.
It's freezing.
Freezing.
CAN YOU DROP US?
>> [laughter]
>> GUYS, WHEN WE WALK BACK UP WE'RE GOING
TO have like perky asses every day.
>> Exactly. But it's good because we need
to move our butts.
>> That person and me close we're keeping
it super super chill. This is our first
restaurant in Mykonos. Just something
super cute and casual but look at this
view.
Oh, it's so pretty. Guys, we're being
attacked by mosquitoes but Lola has What
is this?
>> Uh pasta with mussels.
>> Ooh, and some parmesan. Yum. As to me
and Amy, we got the tuna on risotto.
I'm excited to try this but it does be
looking like some mac and cheese [music]
and like a steak, but it's actually
tuna. First night meal.
This is a welcoming meal.
>> Mhm.
>> Cheers, guys.
>> eat like that
every night.
>> Mhm.
Mhm.
>> That's good.
>> Mhm.
>> What about yours?
>> So stunning.
Wow.
Good morning, guys. It is officially day
one in Mykonos. I just woke up. So,
let's do our skin care, sun prep skin.
[music] I just woke up, so please ignore
the state of me. You can see like my
eyes are puffy, my face is puffy. So, I
want to show you guys my quick easy
morning routine and also how I prep my
skin [music] before I go into the sun.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Then I'm going to go in with my Beauty
of Joseon's [music]
SPF 50 sunscreen. This is definitely one
of my favorite face [music] screens.
This is definitely one of my favorite
sunscreens. And one thing about me, I
will use SPF on my [music] face and my
neck always. And I never ever tan my
face because of which you guys, your
face and your neck
>> [music]
>> age way before your body does. And
that's the first places that's going to
show signs of aging [music] along with
the back of your hand. And as I apply
the cream in the morning, I like to kind
of give myself a little
drainage, [music] open up the drainage
here. I like to use an SPF on my lips as
well. You know, we don't want
dry ass lips. I'm not even a polka dot
girly, but
this grew on me. I really like it. And I
think I'm going to use this as my main
tanning bikini. [music] I want to show
you guys my tanning routine that works
for me so I can get the most golden deep
tan. First of all, the night before make
sure you exfoliate your body and then
you shave everywhere [music] you want to
shave. Then you moisturize really nicely
so your skin is prepared for the next
day. Because it's my first day in
Mykonos and the UV index is so strong, I
like to start with
the Nivea SPF 30.
It's a protective moisturizing cream.
And then you build up. So I like to
start with this
>> [music]
>> and then after my skin gets used to the
heat here, I'm going to change into my
oils. Yeah, cuz you don't want to be
sunburned, trust me.
So [music] once my body gets used to the
sun and it's protected, I'm going to
slowly [music]
go into SPF 30. This is the Nuxe [music]
one. I haven't used this one before but
any SPF 30 oil should work.
>> [music]
>> Um then you're starting to bronze
yourself, you know? And then maybe
tomorrow I'm going to get [music] into
this which is the Hawaiian SPF 15. So
I'm going to skip all the rest and just
[music] start using this for the rest of
the trip. And this is my holy grail. I
love this so much.
>> [music]
>> Um I've been using it for years. I'm
just going to put on a quick little
cover-up. Packing my beach [music] bag
super easy. You always need a bucket hat
to protect your face. Um I got this from
Urban Outfitters [music] and I just love
to cover my face with this so. The
glasses of the day going to be these
Louboutin ones that they gifted me. And
voila, we are done and ready for nice
tanning day at the pool.
Can't wait to see the girls for
breakfast. So let's go. Such a beautiful
day.
I'm waiting on the girls to come for
breakfast but
>> [gasps]
>> so pretty. [laughter]
>> [music]
[music]
>> Guys, this is the most insane breakfast
spread that they made for us. We got the
pancakes,
the veggies, [singing and music] the
fruits, the meat, the cheese, the
pastries. We got some yogurt, granola.
I feel like I'm in heaven right now.
This is stunning.
Wow.
>> [music]
[music]
>> The girls [music] are taking content.
Guys, this is just a perfect day.
Morning, guys. Look at our breakfast.
How cute is this? The chef really showed
out for us. And then, we [music] have
some fruits and grapefruit.
Oh my god, we're so excited for this
one. What is it called again?
>> I forgot. It's just like cheese cheese
bites.
>> Yeah, it's like little cheese bites,
like traditional [music]
Greek. And then, we are with Lola.
This is our breakfast spread, [music]
guys. Look how beautiful it looks.
Every morning, I'm like in awe. Good
morning, guys. I just really wanted to
catch up with you guys. And um after we
were tanning all day, we took a huge
nap. And then, when we woke up, we were
so tired, so we decided not to go out,
which was fine with me because honestly,
I just wanted a chill night. So, it
ended up being super wholesome.
>> Me and Amy did you just like
>> laying on like these sunbeds, looking at
the stars, and it was such a beautiful
experience. We were talking about life
all the way till like 3:00 a.m. And
then, we even saw a shooting star. This
was like the first time I have ever seen
a shooting star, and it was just so
special because we both like made a
wish. I don't know, guys. My heart was
just so full. I really wanted this
holiday to be like therapeutic and not
just like a party holiday or just having
fun and going out all the time, but it
just felt super nice and nurturing to my
soul.
So, yeah, but tonight we'll be outside,
so I'll take you guys along with us, but
I am back on the sunbeds because I want
to tan for a few hours and then after
that, we're going to go into town. Amy
is doing a little shoot for her brand,
so yeah, I'm excited for today.
The current state of me, I still feel
super pale, so the chef was so nice. He
made me a little fruit plate for the
pool. We have some watermelon, we've got
melon, peaches, and my favorite bananas.
I don't know if you guys can see, but
this wind in Mykonos is not a joke. Look
at this.
I've literally had like such a good
standing position.
Guys.
Literally, I'm fighting with the wind.
Hey guys, I am finally back in the room.
Ignore my hair.
It's looking wild because your girl's
had like a good 3-hour session in the
sun, and so, yeah, whatever. Just We're
going to have to take her out soon. I
feel like there's no better feeling than
tanning all day, coming home to a cold
shower, and then getting ready for the
day. But, I'm very excited because Amy's
doing a little shoot for her brand. It's
called Egyptian Bloom, so I'm going to
take you guys along with us. And I
basically want to come and like, you
know, just support her. Also look cute,
take some content of my own. So, I'm
going to just do like my sun-kissed glam
because when I'm on holiday and it's
hot, I don't want to have like
foundation and all of that, you know.
So, first things first, let's do the
brows. But, I don't know what is going
on in Mykonos, guys. When I say the wind
here is not a joke. Like I've been here
this is my third time. Every other time
it's been windy but it hasn't been this
windy. Like I'm just going in with my
Too Faced bronzer and I don't tan my
face at all because tanning your face is
one of the worst thing you guys can do.
It literally ages you so much. I'm so
happy that Euro summer has officially
started. I'm already starting to plan my
other trips for the next few months.
Last night me and Amy were basically
talking about how happy we are that I've
started vlogging because
um both of us rewatched my other Mykonos
trip from last year and it's so nice
that I just have like this digital diary
that I can take you guys along with me
and also I can rewatch it and just be
like wow, your girl has lived. This is
the NARS skin tint. It's my favorite.
It's so lightweight. My secret weapon is
a sun kissed orange blush. This is
what's going to give you guys that
beautiful oh, you've been in the sun,
she's been tanning, vacation glow, you
know? It's in the shade sunset. I
[clears throat] wish I could do the you
know, glowy makeup kind of look but I
just feel like I would look not even
like a glazed donut. I would look like a
donut that's been drenched in oil.
This is the Sweet Beauty Mascara, one of
my favorites. Also tonight is the
semi-final game with England versus
Argentina and I'm so hoping that England
wins. And obviously we are on holiday,
we need our freckles.
What is a vacation without freckles, you
know?
This is the Benefit brow wiz, Too Faced
lip plumping liner. I have you been
using this for over two years. I'm going
to go in with the nude Huda Beauty a
tiny bit.
So I'm using the Urban Decay All
Nighter.
And we are done with makeup. Funny
enough, guys, I literally just did these
plats because I want to create like a
very wavy mermaid kind of look of hair.
Oof, I would I would have been better
off just
>> [music]
>> tonging my hair. Okay, so she did not
turn out how I expected her to turn out.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Oh my god, it looks so much better. Let
me show you guys what I'm thinking of
wearing, okay? Hey guys, this is my
outfit to go into town. I think it's so
cute.
Right?
Pink and yellow literally compliment
each other so well.
I'm obsessed. And cuz it's so windy in
Mykonos, I'm not even going to be hot.
Shades are Louboutin. Bag is Shanaynay.
This top is from Brick Lane.
Um vintage and then Jaded London shorts.
And my Jacquemus heels. I think
I just look so cutie. Okay, we got to
go. Yes, so me and Amy are getting ready
to go to town, guys. How cute she's
setting up her clothes. Work hard, play
hard, right?
This is our first outside of the villa.
>> [laughter]
>> First day actually leaving the hotel,
which is kind of crazy.
>> We've been so tired.
>> [music]
>> So, everyone is here. Do you guys want
to say hi to the vlog?
>> Hi.
>> This She's the model. What's your name?
Introduce yourself.
>> is Selena.
>> First day out.
>> [laughter]
>> To work.
You barely see Mykonos in the daytime
cuz I'm always going out. But it's so
gorgeous.
>> Yeah, so pretty.
>> Oh, wow. Yeah, this area is cute.
>> It's so charming.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Work day.
>> Bring your bestie out for work day
today.
>> And I'm loving it.
>> Guys, I'm having so much fun in town.
Like I feel like we should have been
here from day one, but um
yeah, it's really nice because
I've been trying to get some content in
as well as well as helping Amy. So, it's
just been nice to, you know, be outside.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Wow.
>> [music]
>> And that's a wrap.
>> Yes.
>> Yes, thank you everyone. You were
amazing.
Thank you Anna my love.
>> You're welcome.
>> [music]
>> Okay guys, first official girls night
out.
We have been inside for too long.
>> [laughter]
[music]
>> The wind in New [music] Canaan was
initially nice.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Yeah, swimming is really good.
Did you guys have fun?
First night out. We had so much good
food. What is it called again?
Numidia something
>> Numidia
>> And then we went to Bomboniere.
>> Bomboniere
>> Yeah. What's up?
>> It was so nice.
Yeah.
>> I lost my voice.
>> Yeah, you were.
>> Amy was going wild.
>> Yeah.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Hi guys. It is another beautiful day in
Mykonos. Little recap about last night.
Ask me why we got home at 4:30 a.m. I
didn't sleep until 5:00 a.m. And then we
woke up around 11:00. And I was just
tanning for a few hours. And now we are
on our way to Principote, which is like
a day restaurant that kind of turns into
like a little vibe and everybody is on
the tables. I was in Principote last
time I was in Mykonos as well and I had
the best time. Um also last night we had
so much fun.
And yeah, we are outside. I'll show you
guys my full outfit in a tiny bit. But I
don't know if you guys can see your
girl's got on a little tan. Okay, we're
all matching with wine.
We made it to Principote.
So cute. Go ladies.
>> [music]
[music]
>> The way you [singing] my mind, falling
away in my heart. I know [music]
you feel the same way you are to me.
You know [singing] I'm all you need.
You're where [music] I want to be. My
darling, can't you see?
>> Bathroom break. We're having so much
fun, guys.
>> So much fun.
>> [music]
>> You make me
>> [singing]
[music]
>> HI GUYS.
>> [music]
[music]
>> HI GUYS. THIS IS my official last day in
Greece. So, I've decided to have a
little solo date with myself. I'm going
to this beach club that I've seen and
I've been wanting to try it out. I want
to go and connect with the ocean. I feel
like this whole trip we've just been so
busy, like having fun and like tanning
by the pool. So, it's finally time I go
to the ocean and I want to take you guys
along with me. Sometimes it's good to
have solo time so you can really
reconnect with yourself and take
everything in, manifest. But, yeah, I'm
basically wearing the same bikini this
whole trip because I really want to get
like the same tan line. But, then I
brought an extra pair one so I can
change to it after. Wow guys, the water
here is so stunning.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Guys, I have had the best time being
here, tanning, swimming in the ocean. I
really needed to be in this ocean today
and I feel great. I've just ordered some
lunch. So, we got grilled octopus. So
pretty. And then we have a shrimp salad
as well.
>> [music]
[music]
>> The octopus is so yum.
>> [music]
>> Everything is so fresh and delicious.
[music]
Guys, but yeah guys, that was it for
this week's vlog. I hope you guys
enjoyed the Mykonos vlog. I feel like
this trip was very much more casual and
chill and I really enjoyed it. I just
needed some time away from London. And
yeah, I had such a good time. So, if you
guys enjoyed this vlog, like always,
make sure you like, subscribe and
comment and I will see you in the next
one.